Good morning friends, today we will
tell you about the full selection process of ICICI Bank PO, how the
selection for the post of PO is done in ICICI Bank.
Okay friends, before that,
please subscribe, like,
share and comment on our video so that
you get notifications for every video we upload.
Okay friends, so today we will
know in detail how the
selection process for the PO program is done in ICICI Bank. Okay
friends, so let's go. First of all, you have to have the user ID and password
of ICC Bank.
Okay, if you do
not have this user ID and password, then
you can do a new registration here by clicking on
your mobile number or sign up.
First of all, we will enter the caption in it. We will enter the caption
after that we will enter the caption.
Okay friends, we have entered the caption. We will
click on the login button on it. It will load. After clicking on the
login button, your login will
open like this. When you sign
up, your name, address, application
ID and total will appear. So, check
here the status of the application. We have listed many
vacancies that had come up.  I have
applied on it, okay friends, so in this
way after editing here, we will first
go to the edit option, click on edit profile, as soon as you
click on edit profile,
you will get the browser option here, you
can click on the browser option and enter your CB here, CB means
your resume, okay, along with this, here in the
title, you can enter your name in first name, in
last name, you can enter whatever your name is, if
you are male then you can enter male, if you are
female then you can enter female,
here is the date of birth, you can enter the date of birth,
along with your number, if you have it then
enter it, otherwise leave it blank,
okay, along with mobile number and Aadhar card are
mandatory, okay, after that,
some options are given below,
enter the address and permanent address in it,
after that click on the next button, now when you
click on the next button, like education, the
education part will open,
in education, whatever you have studied,
you can enter your education details here, you can
enter work experience, you
can enter family details, okay  Hey friends, so let's go ahead, I have
updated all of you
and I have also been
selected, I have given GD
and PI as well, so let's see
how the selection is done,
first of all you will have your PT exam, which is going to be held
from 6th December to 6th December and
7th December all over India,
so you will have your PT,
PT is very easy, if you
study even a little then
you can clear it easily, there is no negative marking in it,
friends, okay
friends, first of all you will have to pass your PT
exam, after that you will have to do
OPQ, let's see,
when you pass the PT exam,
your result will come on your email ID,
let's see, we will see the result that came on our email ID,
okay
friends,
see friends, our email ID has been opened, it is
given here on our email ID,
IC Bank Professional Officer Program,
in this we have received an email of 30 marks
and the final
exam is going to be held on 7th and 8th.
For that, slot booking has to be done for the admit card.
For that, I have received an email. Please
see, dear Ravi, congratulations, we are kindly
informing you that
your candidate has been selected in the latest
ICC Bank Question Officer Program for February
2009 batch, that is, in the February 2019 batch,
what has happened, our CB has been
selected. Okay, so
you will get an email like this, here you will also get the username and
password. Okay friends, come on
friends, now our UPT test, which is going to be
held from 7th December 2018 to 8th December, will be of
60 minutes, there will be simple
questions. Okay, so you will have to pass it.
When you pass it, you will get
an email that we had given the November base
exam, I was selected in that
and I had completed the PT,
cracked the PT, so you have received an email for that,
we will show you that mail as well.
We will show you that mail as well. Let us show you that mail.
Look here, we will show you that mail.
Friend, the mail that we received on September 4, for
which we had given the PT exam, we had
received its mail in August, so let
us show you that, see what kind of mail comes,
see, it came in the November 2018 batch, it came for the SSC
Professional Officer Requirement
Process Occupational Personality Assessment
2018 batch, the ID was given in it,
what happens in this OPQ is that you will be given some
questions, they check your mentality, what kind of a
person you are, so first of all
when you get this mail, you will have to complete the OPQ,
some time limit has been given to complete the OPQ, so
you can do the OPQ within that time limit, you
can do it at home on your laptop, okay
friends, you have to see in it that whatever interests you, whatever interests you, they will
ask you about your personal interest, do you
like to be in the crowd or do you
like to be among people, such
questions will come in it, there will be no extra questions in it, there is
no fear of failing or passing in it, okay  Yes friends,
in this only IIC Bank
checks your mentality, after that when this OPQ is completed,
after that they will give you another mail for GD and PI,
let's see that
I have received a mail for GD and PI,
let's open that mail as well and see
what is given in that mail,
friends, we had completed the OPQ,
so on 7th September we received a mail, one
more mail came in which it is given,
II Bank Professional Officer Requirement
Process, Group Discussion, Personal Interview
Process was given here, dear Avi
Roshan, it was given here, we are please to invite you to
participate in the next
round of the selection process of the
Probationary Officer Program, the process will
consist of the Occupational Personality
Question or Group Discussion and Question
Interview, after this when we complete the OPQ,
our GD and Question
Interview are going to take place, so on
which date is the Question Interview, which date was it, it was on 24th
September, the location was in Patna
Chandragupta Institute of Management Patna
Mithapur Institute Area Near Gate Number
One Bus Stand Patna
8001 timing was 12 AM so we
went there we gave GD we gave PI there in GD there are
five topics given in it before going to GD
you were given five topics
in it you can see what five topics we
got for GD what documents we needed for GD and PI let's
see that first so for GDR PI a
copy of this mail was
required a copy of latest CV was
required a PAN card was required Aadhar card was required
SC ST certificate was required
self attested photocopy of 10th MA
marksheet marksheet of graduation marksheet
you had to
reach the centre with all these things okay
friends along with us the topic
on which group discussion was going to be held was the first
topic role of digitization in the banking
sector this was one topic and total five
topics  The second topic was Unique
Identification Number for Every Individual
and the next topic I was going to have was a
group discussion called Technology
Changing the Face of Education and the next
topic was a total of five topics Social
Networking in Our Lips and the next
topic
was Generalization and Specialization. So
friends, when you are going to have a GD, when
you complete the PT and
complete the OPQ, then you will have a GD, so
you will get an email five to six days before that in which the
topic of GD will be given,
you have to read that topic thoroughly and
understand it topic wise well and along with that
you have to do a
group discussion on any one of these topics, just keep in mind that the
total discussion in this is
in English, no one speaks Hindi there,
if someone speaks Hindi then you
can do it in Hindi but
no one speaks Hindi there, total people speak in English,
so you will have to do the group discussion in English
and it
is necessary to speak in the group discussion, if you do not speak then you will be
disqualified from there itself.
Friends, my topic was
Specialization and Generalization,
which I got easily.
I spoke only two to three sentences and was
selected.
After that, we had a personal interview. After the personal
interview, I received another
email, which I did
not read and could not reach,
due to which I was not selected. So, the
next exam is on the 7th and 8th.
This time we will appear for this exam. In
this way, after your D and PI are
completed, after that
you will get an email. You have a
training of about one year for training. It takes place
at Sikkim Manipal University, Bangalore.
After completing that training, you will be sent as a bank manager or
branch manager.
Okay, friends, this was the
entire selection process of ACC Bank. So, I hope
you liked this video very much.
Yes, if you liked it, then share it,
like it, comment on it
and don't forget to subscribe so that whenever we
post a video, you get a notification as soon as possible.
Thank you.